[MOM 9A] You did a great job
Mister Ishimori!
Your daughter
is so well behaved!
[MOM 9B]
She's such a good girl!
Wish my kids were that sweet.
[UKA'S DAD] She was
all the rage of the park!
One of the moms said
she was jealous of us!
[UKA'S MOM]
Aw!
-[UKA'S DAD] Uka.
-[gasps]
Your mother and I are
endlessly proud of you.
Now and always.
[UKA'S DAD]
Uka, put that away!
[UKA (CHILD)]
I wanna help.
I wanted to buy her
a child-safe knife,
but for now, letting
mommy's little helper
use a fruit knife
should be okay.
Can't that wait until she's had
a chance to grow up a bit?
Don't know what I'd do
if something happened
to my little girl.
So, slow down.
You can leave
all the difficult stuff to us.
You're gonna be class rep?
To what purpose?
I'm not quite sure.
The other students
nominated me.
[UKA'S DAD]
That sounds like a lot of work.
Don't overwhelm yourself.
The title wouldn't even help
school applications much,
so I'll tell your teacher
to assign someone else.
Just let your old man
handle everything.
I'll make sure
it all works out perfectly!
[UKA]
He does this...for me.
I'm headed out!
[UKA'S MOM]
See you later!
♪
[UKA]
All my life,
my world has felt so small.
Wrapped in my cocoon,
safe and sound.
Good morning, Uka!
-[Uka gasps]
-[AYUMI] Gimme some love!
♪
-Whoops.
-[Satoru chuckles]
I think we might've broken her!
[indistinct chatter]
I hope all my lovely pupils
had a nice time
over summer break!
Why do we have to be here?
I got stuck
in my nocturnal mode.
Well, at least none of you
decided to drop out this year.
-Hmm.
-[gasps]
[ABE]
Miura? Miura?
No, don't leave us!
I'm not dropping out,
so stop yelling at me.
[MARIN]
Overslept on the first day?
[KAI]
Yeah.
♪
Hmm.
[gasps]
♪
Good morning!
Hi!
[trembling]
And, uh, welcome.
[YUKINO]
Dude, where did that come from?
I dunno.
It's part of my morning ritual.
Gotta say hi to Ishimori.
[NAGANO]
But why?
[YASUSHI]
Nah, I get it!
The day doesn't really
start until you see her.
Like, "Yep,
I'm ready for school now."
[TONBO] Right?
She's like our personal Jizo
watching over our class!
[Kai chuckles]
Nice start to your second term.
[gasps]
[laughs]
[UKA'S DAD] At some point,
my little girl grew up
and stopped holding
her dad's hand.
[gasps]
♪
[UKA]
I've tried.
[KAI] When you get home,
ask your dad
if you can download an app.
[UKA]
But for some reason,
I haven't been able
to ask him yet.
[YURU] We actually
got out early today!
[AYUMI]
Let's karaoke!
[YURU]
Ah! It's perfect!
All of us wanted to find a time
before your curfew
to hang out after class!
We actually talked about you
a lot over summer break!
Our class wouldn't be
the same without ya!
[Uka chuckles]
[UKA]
I don't know why,
but it still bothers me.
[TAO]
We're here.
[UKA]
There it is!
KARAOKE CENTER
Look at how many different
rooms they have!
And drinks too?
Be careful not to get lost.
[yawns]
Did you not sleep well
last night?
♪
Couldn't stop thinking.
[chuckles softly]
About what?
-The girl in front of me.
-[gasps]
[trembling]
Just kidding.
[nervous chuckle]
♪
[AYUMI]
Hey, Uka!
Let's get in there!
[TEACHER 9A] What do you think
you're doing here?
-Ah?
-Hm?
-We are really sorry!
-[TEACHER 9A] Name and class?
Isn't that the uniform
from Shinsei?
[TEACHER 9A] You already
know what the rules are.
Didn't think girls from
such a prestigious school
would come here.
Uka, isn't that the place
you were gonna go?
[YURU]
But you went with Hachimitsu?
That's a...choice.
[UKA'S DAD] I know Shinsei will
be the perfect fit for you.
Their curriculum
and their principles
are all top notch.
And it's a girls-only
establishment,
so you won't encounter
the wrong types of boys.
You didn't answer anything?
What came over you
during the test?
Our dream's over.
Shinsei doesn't do make-ups.
You have no choice left
but to go to Hachimitsu.
[SUBORDINATE 9A]
Wow, high schoolers sure
are different than in my day.
How bad of a parent
do you have to be
to let your kids go out
looking like that?
I ask myself the same question
about our youth all the time.
Wait, those are
Hachimitsu uniforms.
Oh, yeah, that makes sense,
since the rules
are supposedly lax there.
What parent would let their--
My daughter attends Hachimitsu.
-Sorry, sir.
-It's okay.
[gasps]
♪
Ah?
[SUBORDINATE 9A]
Sir?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
My kid's different.
[KAI]
What's up?
You okay?
[UKA]
I learned...
that I can walk on my own.
[UKA'S DAD] You can leave
all the difficult stuff to us.
[KAI] Gotta see it through
to the end.
[UKA'S DAD]
Don't overwhelm yourself.
[KAI]
'Cause ya can't just quit.
You make the rules now.
♪
[UKA]
He taught me I can be more.
That I'm not helpless.
My world's been reborn.
My values are changing.
[UKA'S DAD]
You have no choice left
but to go to Hachimitsu.
[AYUMI] Our class wouldn't be
the same without ya!
[UKA]
I belong somewhere,
but dad doesn't approve.
I'm not pushing him away,
but...
Miura?
Be honest with me.
Am I betraying my dad's trust?
[UKA'S DAD]
Uka...
your mother and I are
endlessly proud of you.
Now and always.
[UKA'S MOM]
Welcome home.
Is Uka back in her room?
[UKA'S MOM]
She's here.
Yeah.
I hope everything
went well at work, Dad.
I, uh...
She told me she went to sing
karaoke after her classes!
What a day!
With whom?
With my friends.
[UKA'S DAD]
Those are your friends?
[clearing throat]
I would expect you
to keep better company.
You shouldn't hang out
with delinquents like that.
[Uka gasps]
[UKA'S DAD] You should
really find suitable friends.
Ones, a bit more respectable.
[Uka gasps]
But...they are respectable!
[UKA'S DAD]
Well, you could've fooled me.
[UKA]
Please, Dad.
Uka, you're done there.
I won't let you
go to Hachimitsu.
You'll be transferring.
Hold on.
Uka's not here yet?
Do you think she might've
come down with something?
Not one to cut class.
[AYAKA]
Oh, morning, Mr. Abe.
[MIRU] Yo, teach!
Ishimori stayin' home today?
[TONBO] Yeah!
Did ya hear from her folks?
[YASUSHI]
Abe? Hey!
C'mon, bro.
Hmm.
Apparently, Ishimori's absent
for the indefinite future.
[all gasp]
Say what?
I just got out
of an impromptu meeting
with her father.
He wants her to drop out
of Hachimitsu High.
[gasps]
♪
[UKA'S DAD]
You'll be transferring.
Hachimitsu fails my standards.
My daughter deserves better.
But, Dad, you can't!
I don't wanna transfer!
It isn't good for you
to hang out
with miscreants like those.
-[UKA] It is.
-You would be seen
around a boy like that?
You mean Miura?
He's the most important person
in the world to me.
I can't lose him like this!
You can't decide
what's right for me.
There's so many things
you don't know!
[gasps]
Ah!
[UKA'S DAD]
I'm pulling you out of school.
Use this time
to think carefully.
[UKA] Just when things
were finally getting better.
[all gasp]
[AYUMI]
You're joking, right?
-She's transferring?
-But why?
He said our school
isn't conducive to her growth.
[YUKINO]
In second term?
Furthermore,
that our class has said
some unacceptable things
to Ishimori.
That she's been bullied.
[YUKINO]
He thinks we're bullying her?
Why would he think that?
She's been called names.
Some were comparing her
to a stone.
Some teased her
for being quiet.
And I've been told
she was mocked
for having a 5 o'clock curfew.
[all gasp]
We haven't been
laughing at her!
What the hell?
Like we'd do that!
I can't believe all that
came from Ishimori's dad.
If you're gonna get
on our backs about anything,
at least find something
we legit did.
[NAGANO]
Is Ishimori saying that, too?
Absolutely not!
Uka knows how much
we care about her,
and she would never
say stuff like that!
-[SHIRAISHI] Hold on!
-[TAO] We'll come, too!
Hey, wait!
Class isn't over yet, you know?
Calm down!
[indistinct chatter]
Her father's getting
in her way.
Poor Uka.
[indistinct chatter]
-[AYUMI] Pardon!
-[UKA'S DAD] Ah?
You're Uka's dad, aren't you?
There's been a horrible
misunderstanding!
We've never said a bad word
about your daughter!
Kids in another class
already told me everything.
I promise we can explain this
if you just give us a chance!
[UKA'S DAD]
Please, save your breath.
[gasps]
Bro, do you really
not understand
the difference between laughing
at someone and with them?
[SHIRAISHI]
Stop it, Tonbo!
That difference is something
I'll decide for her.
And "bro?"
You should call me "sir."
I promise, if you heard about
her getting bullied,
all that happened
in junior high.
Don't lump all of us together
with those twerps.
Oh?
Quit lying.
If she was bullied then,
I would know.
She went to school
happy as could be.
Every day for three years.
Never skipped.
Now, then...
I believe you're missing
your classes.
Say goodbye to Uka.
She'll never associate
with you again.
-Don't make her go!
-Let's step back!
We only made things worse here.
This backfired on us.
But I don't get it.
How did he not know
about the bullying?
All that time?
Ah!
[sighs]
[beeping]
What did you tell my daughter
to brainwash her?
She's been changing on her own.
[UKA'S DAD]
Stay away from Uka.
So, that's it, then.
You're putting her
back in her cage?
Shut your mouth,
you little pissant.
My daughter doesn't need you.
[UKA'S MOM]
Honey, look!
There!
She passed!
-I'm so proud of you, Uka!
-[chuckles]
♪
[gasps]
Ah!
♪
[gasps]
[UKA]
Ayumi! Miura!
[AYUMI]
Was that to us?
[SATORU] I dunno know.
Is she a friend of yours?
I don't think
I've ever seen her before.
[gasps]
[TOMOYA]
You, Kai?
-Not a clue.
-[gasps]
♪
It was just a dream,
but it felt
so painfully realistic.
♪
[phone vibrating]
[gasps]
AYUMI CALLING
-Hello?
-[AYUMI] You answered!
-[AYUMI] I'm so relieved!
-Good to hear your voi--
[AYUMI] You're not really
transferring schools?
Please, don't leave me.
[weeping]
I'll miss you so much.
Ah!
-Ishimori?
-Speaker, girl!
[TAO] Why are you letting
him push you around?
[UKA]
I can't go.
[TAO]
Get it together!
Are you still there?
[UKA]
I want to stay here.
[UKA'S DAD]
Who are you talking to?
-[UKA] No one!
-I'll take that.
I know you're upset.
But please, listen.
My classmates
are important to me.
They've helped me so much!
No matter what, I can't just
lose them like this!
I won't!
I refuse to transfer schools!
♪
Understood.
You've made
your feelings clear.
You obviously don't care
about your father anymore...
so do what you want.
I'll hold on
to your phone for now.
[door closes]
[UKA]
No.
♪
[VOICE 9A]
The phone you have called
is either out of range
or has been powered off.
Please try again
at a later time.
♪
[UKA]
Have I become too greedy?
Will I have to give up
one thing to protect another?
Do I really have to decide
what I'm ready to lose?
What would Miura say
about this?
-[tapping on window]
-Hm?
♪
Good, you're up.
[gasps]
♪
[KAI]
Hey!
Ah!
[Kai chuckles]
Is it raining?
♪
So...your phone's off.
Did he take it?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Did ya hear?
He came down
to the school today.
[UKA]
What'd he say?
Nothing much.
Just accused us
of bullying his daughter.
[gasps]
[KAI] Guess "banter"
and "bullying" sound alike.
We tried to tell him,
but...he wouldn't listen.
♪
I made everyone feel bad.
This should've only
affected me!
[crying]
But...I don't know
who I'm supposed
to hold on to anymore.
[KAI]
Hold on to everyone.
[gasps]
You have a dad
who cares about you.
You made friends
with your entire class.
[KAI]
It's all important.
So...you'll just
have to hold on to both.
Got it?
[gasps]
[UKA]
Yeah.
[KAI] Good.
Feeling better?
[UKA]
Yeah.
[KAI]
You ready to take care of it?
[UKA]
Yeah.
[KAI]
Good girl.
Well...I'm going home.
♪
[chuckles]
"Good girl?"
Did I really say that?
Who am I supposed to be to you?
[UKA]
You're the man that I love.
Uh...how are you gonna
get back down--
I'll just sprout wings.
I can't wait to see
what you're gonna do next.
GOODBYE, BUMBLING DAYS
[UKA]
Hey, Mom, where's Dad?
[UKA'S MOM] Huh?
I guess he went out on a walk.
He was here a second ago.
Uh, hey, what's up?
[panting]
[UKA]
He takes walks when he's upset.
I know his route.
I can catch him!
I'll tell him...for their sake.
And for his!
[YURU]
Ayumi, try not to freak out.
[AYUMI]
What do you expect me to do?
Uka might actually
get transferred
if we don't do
something to help her!
[YURU]
I get it, girl.
But it's not our place
to jump in the middle of that.
[SHIRAISHI] Not like any of us
understand the relationship
she has with her parents.
Well, if mine did
something like that,
I'd never go back home.
[sighs]
I'm still a little curious.
Why didn't she tell them
that she was being bullied
in junior high?
[panting]
[AYUMI] Maybe she thought
they'd freak out.
Or she didn't
want to burden them.
So, she suffered alone,
instead.
All that time,
she was putting on a fake smile
to convince them she was fine.
But now she can tell them
what she thinks!
I wanna be there
with her, fighting!
She and I feel the same way,
so I can't just watch!
You'll see, I'm gonna go
bring her back to us!
-[YURU] Wait. Ayumi!
-[SHIRAISHI] Slow down!
[TAO]
We'll come too!
[Shiraishi and Tao panting]
So, where are you and I going?
♪
[UKA]
I was always lying.
If I said something,
I thought that would only serve
to make my parents sad.
So, I didn't.
For where I was...
that was the best I could do.
But...
He isn't here.
Maybe he got further ahead
of me than I...
[gasps]
[UKA]
But now?
Look, this way!
Hey, Uka!
[UKA]
Things are different,
and I can do better!
I have to tell you.
I lied.
Back in junior high,
I was bullied every day.
[gasps]
♪
[UKA'S MOM]
Oh!
All those years,
I didn't have a single friend.
Every day was more miserable
than the last.
-[whimpering]
-[UKA] But...I kept it from you
so you wouldn't know.
So...I'm sorry.
♪
But now it's all right, and--
-[UKA'S DAD] When did it start?
-[gasps]
Why did you think
you couldn't tell us about it?
[UKA]
Oh, no.
I didn't mean
to lead with that.
[REMI]
Mind if I butt in?
Most of the crap
she's talking about
came from me.
[gasps]
You're her bullies?
[REMI] How about listening
for a sec before you jump me?
Back in junior high,
your little girl acted like
such a mess
whenever we were around,
it was hard not
to get pissed at her.
But you shoulda seen her
at the beach the other day.
She came right up to me
and said hello.
Way it used to be,
she'd shut down anytime
I took a step near her.
Till she met these guys.
If I had to guess, they're
the ones who changed it.
If you're wondering why,
she probably went to Hachimitsu
to meet people like them.
♪
-[UKA] Dad.
-[gasps]
I get it.
This all scares you.
But I am not going anywhere.
I can take care of myself.
I can do more than you know.
Please don't worry anymore.
I promise I'll be fine.
Of course...
I still need you.
But I am going back on Monday.
Hachimitsu's my home.
♪
[UKA'S DAD]
Uka...lift your head.
[gasps]
♪
[UKA'S DAD] I apologize
for the misunderstanding.
♪
Please...
look after my daughter.
♪
[sighs]
Hello!
My name is Ayumi Endou.
I'm a Sagittarius,
and I live with my mom, dad,
and one older sister.
And my pet bunny!
I may dress a little crazy,
but I am sane!
She'll be fine with me!
I love her!
[YURU]
Oh, my turn!
I'm Yuru Hashimoto!
My name's weird,
but my parents are normal!
[SERINA] [sighs]
Serina Kanno!
I'm a Gemini.
Blood type B.
And I love Uka, too!
[UKA]
So...how'd I do?
Nailed it.
I'm Kai, I'm an Aquarius.
And while I may be a pissant,
I take care of her.
[UKA'S DAD] Not quite ready
to accept you so easily.
♪
[UKA]
Dad.
♪
Mom.
This is it.
♪
This is the new world
I've found.
♪
TO BE CONTINUED